

ABOUT



IT Professional with ±6 years of experience in software development and in creating innovative solutions to system issues. I am a team player with strong programming experience to build and operate secure systems. Able to explain complex software problems in easy-to-reach terms.

KONTAK

- - +62 821-1090-6990
- manusiacoding29@gmail.com
- mctechnologyofficial.github.io
- 0
- Haji Dimun 3 Street, Depok, West Java, Indonesia

SKILL

- PHP Native / Framework (Laravel, Codeigniter)
- ReactJS, VueJS, NodeJS
- Bootstrap
- JQuery
- Flutter Framework
- C, C++, C#
- VB.NET, ASP.NET
- MySQL, MongoDB, Firebase

FAWWAZ HUDZALFAH SAPUTRA

PROGRAMMER

EXPERIENCE

PT Telkom Akses | Programmer Analyst

Jan 2021 - May 2022

- Build / develop software espesically at the requirements, design stage and partly in the constitution / implementation stage
- Build / develop a framework / library for use in software development by programmer

PT Telkomsel | Back-End Programmer

May 2020 - Jan 2021

- Managed up to 3 projects or tasks at a given time while under pressure
- Created 1 website to control the network per point in a specific city using ReactJS and NodeJS technologies

PT Indotrading | Lead Programmer

Jan 2017 - Jan 2020

- Reponsible for the technical specifications of the project and managing the overall code development process
- Created reports from the Programmer Tasks for the User

EDUCATION

- IPWIJA University (2022 Now) Faculty of Information System
- SMK PGRI 1 Depok (2017 2020) Software Engineering